This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era, a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the One Piece, the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the
Pirates. Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit, set sail
to become the next King of the Pirates. As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles, they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government, which will use any means necessary
to stop them. This is exciting! I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue, the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line
to the New World. Separated from the rest of his crew, Luffy has finally arrived at Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace. In their attempt to save Ace, the Whitebeard Pirates have launched
an all-out assault on any Marines standing in their way. And now, the battle is really starting
to heat up. Now, come, come! Giant! Rise up!
Hard battles, one after another. Devil fruit eaters versus devil fruit eaters.
He toppled a giant all on his own! Hell yeah, Straw Hat! You took him down with one punch!
Whoa! I'm back!
Hey, Straw Hat! If you were aiming to get their attention, I think you've succeeded.
Do not let the Foremost Group advance any further. Haul them off and put that rookie in the ground.
Damn it! Make them pay!
Aaaaaaah!
Enough beating around the bush. Let's launch a frontal attack and join Bob's inside the bay.
Whatever it takes to save Ace.
Drive them back with everything you've got!
Aaaaaaah!
We gotta fight the Vice-Admirals, too? Those guys are too strong!
I don't think we have any other options.
Well, this is gonna be rough, but do it for Ace!
Aaaaaaah!
They're all going to get themselves killed!
Bazooka unit ready! Now fire at Whitebeard!
Look out!
Damn it! Please don't do this!
Aaaaaaah!
Now slash him to pieces!
Aaaaaah!
You're not gonna stop me from saving my brother, so you might as well get out of my way!
Luffy, why do you care so much?
Why do any of them care?
I deserve to die like this.
Why can't they see I'm not worth risking their lives for?
Aaaaaah!
We, the 2nd Division of the Whitebeard Pirates, will save our commander, Ace, no matter what
the cost!
Yes!
Please don't do this.
Just stop.
Just let me die like I'm supposed to.
Ace!
You're my brother!
Aaaaaah!
You can't be this stupid!
Stop, Luffy!
Turn around, Bobbs!
Bobbs!
What is it, Ace?
I'm ready.
Ready to accept whatever I deserve.
I'll accept any help that's offered to me.
But I'll also accept any punishment.
Either one.
Whichever comes first.
I'm just ready for all this to end.
On my signal, man!
Fire!
I'm gone!
Aaaaaah!
Fall down!
Look at that punk.
It's like he's trying to steal the show.
Like this is his war.
It should be Captain Buggies.
I think it's time, boss.
You gotta stand up and show the world who you are.
This is the perfect moment for you to defeat Whitebeard.
Maybe I will.
Maybe I will!
I gotta keep stalling.
This war is completely bonkers.
There's nothing but monsters on both sides.
I'll just keep my head down and stay quiet.
Hey, you.
Clown nose.
What the hell did you just say to me?
Are you cruising for a bruising punk?
Huh?
I take it back!
I thought I recognized you.
You worked for Roger back when you were just a brat.
It's been a while, but it doesn't look like things have changed too much.
I can't believe I just threatened him!
He's gonna kill me!
Yep, he's a dead man!
His only chance is to run!
Holy crap, it's Whitebeard!
And he's speaking to him!
That is like the coolest thing I've ever seen!
It's just further proof that you are a genuine living legend!
Don't they realize I'm about to die?
Must be nice if it's not your ass on the line!
You've got an entire battalion of prisoners.
Now you're not planning on challenging me, are you?
That right he is!
Oh, sorry about that.
You probably wanted to tell him yourself.
You give him hell, Captain Buggy!
I don't have much choice thanks to you morons!
Yeah, we meet at last!
Now prepare yourself!
Geez, he is pushing his luck right off the edge of a cliff!
Oh yeah?
It doesn't bother me if you're hungry for a fight.
But if you beat me, then what's next?
Might be more navy soldiers than you can handle on your own.
Oh hell, if I'm being honest, they're more than I can handle.
Now I'm not one to back down from a challenge,
but it would make more sense to form an alliance.
Once we're done, then you can kick my ass.
Oh holy crap!
Whitebeard actually recognizes you as his brother in arms!
He considers you an equal!
No, he called him a brat like one minute ago!
Don't tell me you're gonna try to take on the navy!
You don't really think you can win, do you?
Well, yeah.
I've just gotta go all out!
He's completely lost his grip on reality!
Seriously?
Oh, I've got goosebumps!
You know what?
Maybe I can do this!
Maybe I really was destined to be king!
Standing on top of the world!
I think you might be onto something!
Let's join forces and take down the navy!
Ah!
This is amazing!
Man!
It's too much!
Alright, you win, Whitebeard!
I'll partner with you!
But only cause you're begging me to!
Huh?
So arrogant!
Oh well!
That's Captain Bunny!
What's wrong with him?
Did he pull some kind of brainwashing technique on these idiots?
Think of these idiots!
Hmm.
Well, that guy is unbelievably easy to manipulate.
He's a fool to say the least.
But the prisoners he's got behind him are something else entirely.
The last thing we need now is more enemies.
Now, back to the war!
All ships in the back!
Come forward and deploy backup!
It's time to show them what we're made of!
I have a report, sir.
All of the pirates stationed in the rear are currently heading this way!
It took them long enough!
Calling the forward unit at the bay head!
Change the formation as the fleet admiral ordered!
Prepare to deploy strategy!
All units!
Start backing up!
But keep fighting!
And make sure you retreat slowly!
Did they stop firing on us?
Yeah!
It looks like they're starting to pull back!
Those navy bastards are starting to buckle!
One more push and we got them!
Enemy ships on both sides!
It's too late now!
They can't stop us from charging the bay!
Right!
Now's our chance to finally join Pops at the center of the fight!
Putta putta putta putta!
Click!
Come in!
This is Whitebeard!
Put Squard on the line, now!
Oh!
Pops!
You need Captain Squard?
Well he um...
He was right here just a few moments ago but now uh...
The thing is I'm not seeing him anywhere sir!
Yeah go figure!
All that tough talk and then he's not even around when you ask for his help!
Hmm...
Well so it goes!
Get me the DeKalvin brothers then!
Hey Pops!
What's up?
Yeah Pops!
I want you to follow my lead!
Take command of all pirate divisions around you!
You got it!
Yes sir!
And what's the command?
Just focus on sinking the approaching navy ships!
What?
But Pops!
This is the best shot we've had at making a frontal assault since the battle got started!
Yeah you're not giving up are ya?
Just trust me on this one!
I've got a bad feeling about those ships!
Well you can count on us Pops!
That's right!
We got it!
We'll spread the order to the other captain!
Really?
That straight from Pops?
Well alright then!
I can take the right side!
I got it!
We'll take the left side!
Right!
Understood!
We'll join in on the right side too!
Okay!
If that's what Pops wants!
My ship can take any direction!
Whatever works best!
Squad's missing?
No!
I haven't seen him lately!
How unusual!
Sure thing!
We'll take the left flank!
Excuse me fleet admiral sir!
But the pirates of the new world have altered their battle tactics!
Yes!
It seems they've turned to the sides!
They suddenly started attacking the approaching Navy ships!
Your bluff's been called!
Whitebeard must have sensed something's wrong!
So I tried a cheap trick and he didn't fall for him!
I'll admit it was a bit too obvious!
But still he can't prevent the inevitable just because he sees it coming!
You can't prevent the inevitable just because he sees it coming!
CaptionCube
Ah, damn it. There's too many of them. I don't see how we'll ever break through.
Death!
Wee-haw!
Yee-haw!
Whoa, Eva, you're all right!
Eva, we've got to clear these jerks out to get to Ace!
Jinbei!
Fishman Karate!
Death!
It's gum-gum!
Five thousand brick fists!
Wee-fazooka!
Ah!
On we go!
I'm coming!
Do not let them get any farther!
Ah, Straw Hat! You don't really think you can get past me!
Him again?!
I shall be your opponent this time!
What are you talking about?!
My karate skills will be more than adequate to thwart you, alone.
That's a mighty fine speech! I'm impressed!
Yes!
But that's good!
Cause once I take care of you, my zombies can run wild again!
You keep moving, Luffy! Don't waste a moment on this villain!
I won't! Thanks a lot, Jinbei!
I can't believe I'm letting Straw Hat slip past me!
So, Jinbei, are you really so delusional that you think you can beat me on dry land, huh?!
Oh, man! I liked it better when Jinbei was on our side!
The Seven Warlords are a crucial part of our forces!
It just doesn't seem right to fight each other!
Huh?
What's up? Is something wrong?
It's my shadow!
Yes! Yes! Yes! Yes!
Now, suffer damnation, Navy soldiers! For your shadows shall fight for me!
Easy!
Easy, easy, easy!
Since you know all of my secrets, Jinbei, did you know that my power grows exponentially with every shadow I consume?
I'm guessing not all you wouldn't have so foolishly challenged me!
So you got bigger! Pointless! The power you flaunt is stolen from others! Your selfishness is not just strength, but weakness!
Shut up! We'll see how smug you are when I turn you into sushi!
And I'm gonna add your shadow to my collection!
You'll spend the rest of your life toiling within my darkness! How does that sound?
I'll take that shadow now!
You're rather fast! You're such a hulking fellow, aren't you?
You're the only hulking fellow here, you imbecile!
Fishman Karate!
Sharkskin Pomp Thrust!
Shark Brick Fist!
in the end you gave up those coveted shadows of yours rather easily perhaps you should train
yourself more it's time you gave up and let me pass i'm done with you my only concern is ace
you don't get to lecture me this fight's not over
that's straw hat move to shigi
jeez it's you smokey i finally found you about time huh no straw boy huh kuma would you just stop
already oh no no no no oh yeah i forgot this weapon is tipped with c prism stone you cheater
you're fine second gear i'm not gonna let you get away this time come come
jump got me
white launcher
you're a lot stronger than you used to be
you're a real force to be reckoned with
i hate to tell you though you're still not strong enough to beat me
whoa come on our smoker just been straw hats he's amazing damn it you cheap jerk move that thing
after all this time i finally understand the truth
i know why dragon really helped you if it weren't for him that day you'd be dead
you may have had dragon to save you in log town but no one's gonna save you today
this sucks get your filthy heads off him
my body's smoke how'd she hit me you can't just kick him he ate a logia fruit
wait a sec why did the pirate empress just save straw hat hey hancock what the hell's wrong with you
don't tell me you're resigning from the warlord shut your mouth the screaming fury in my heart has
rendered me deaf to your words how dare you pin my beloved down with your boorish club and threaten him
you will die for your actions i've never felt this angry in my entire life i'll feed you piece
by piece to wild animals the coochers hockey is overwhelming thanks hancock of course also i'm happy
you got my name right again please listen that's enough kuma look it's me have you forgotten my face
if you don't stop friendship be damned i will fight back i don't know what kind of a history you two
have but it doesn't matter trust me emporio ivankov there's really no use in talking to him as he is
now doflamingo what are you saying is something wrong with him you're clearly a friend of bartholomew
kuma's so i doubt you'll take this well the man you knew as the tyrant kuma is not the man you see
before you now because that man is dead huh but that can't be true
how can kuma be dead
facing kuma on the battlefield ivankov reveals they were once friends however he was pleased to his old
companion fall on deaf ears as kuma continues his attacks in a sea of confusion only doflamingo seems
to know the truth on the next one piece kuma's transformation eva's blow of anger i'm gonna be king of the pirates